（ヘカドス）
よう！貴様が末子殿の契約者か。→
Hey there.
So this fool is the
Youngest's Contract Holder?
我が名は　ヘカドス。
ベヘモット３４柱師団　第八の柱。
My name is Hecadoth!
The 8th Pillar of Behemoth's
34 Pillar Division.
（ヒルダ）
とにかく　一定距離以上　奴に
近づくな！その上で引き付けろ。
Anyway, keep a fixed distance from him.
And hold his attention on you!
貴様は死んでも構わん。
坊っちゃまの安全が第一だ。
I don't care if you die, but the
Master's safety is foremost!
わかったな！！
Got it?!
（男鹿）いくぜ！ベル坊！！
（ベル坊）
アイ～ダブッ！
Here we go, Baby Beel!
ン～～！！
（ヘカドス）はっ！
おらあああ！！
ガルルルル！！
ゼブルブラストォ～！！
Zebel Blast!
驚いたぞ　貴様。
末子殿の力を操れるのか！
You surprise me, human!
You can control the Youngest's power?
そのまま　潰れちまえっ！！
Now just up and die!
（ヘカドス）ガッ！！
あ…。
だが　悪いな。
その程度では虫も潰せんぞ。
But, I hate to say...
You won't be killing me
with something like that.
《マジかよ…》
You're kiddin' me...
いや…十分だ。
あっ！
No, it was plenty.
遅い…。
Too late.
男鹿っ！
Oga!
よぉっし。
やるじゃねえか　ヒルダ。
Right then. Good going, Hilda.
テメエ見直…。
ニョ！
I misjudged y-
あっ…。
あぁ　貴様…最初から　これが…。
You... planned this... from the start...?
女など　くれてやる。
You can have that woman.
一番　邪魔なのは侍女悪魔
お前だ！
The biggest obstacle is
the Demon Maidservant.
あっ…うっ。
You.
ヒルダっ！！
Hilda!
全ては　焔王様のために。
Everything is for Lord En.
（焔王）あああ　な…。
お願いしま～す。
なんじゃあ
あの侍女悪魔の群れは！？
What's with all these Demon Maidservants?!
Which Demon do they serve?
どの悪魔に仕えておる！？
（サテュラ）さ　さあ…。
おおっ！！
I-I have no idea...
（ヨルダ）あ　坊っちゃま！→
Master!
イザベラ…このままで大丈夫？
Isabella, are you sure we have time for this?
Behemoth's servants are probably
already making their move.
ベヘモットの部下たち
おそらく　もう動き出してるわよ。
（イザベラ）
ベルゼ様には酷ですが
捨て置くことしかできません。
It may be harsh for Beelze-sama,
yet we have no choice but
to leave him on his own.
私たちには　焔王坊っちゃまを
見守るという使命が…。
Our mission is to watch
over and protect Lord En.
Can I have a picture?
写真いいっすか～！？
え？
（通行人）
えっ　美人だ！お店どこすか！？
（シャッター音）
Whoa! Hot girls!
Which café are you from?
な　なんなんだ　お前ら～！
What's wrong with you people?
うぉ～！こ　これは　ストリート
キング　オブ　ファイターズ！
This is...
Street King of Fighters!
And... 4?!
しかも４じゃと！？
ネットワーク対戦も可。
You can fight other people online?!
うふ　これで余も
ネトゲ　デビューじゃ。
This'll be my online-game debut!
おい　サテュラ　金を！
Satura, hand me money!
サ　サテュラ？イザベラ？
ヨル…ダ？
Satura, Isabella... Yol...da...?
ちょっと　アンタらね～！
Hold it, people!
な　なんだ！？
どきなさいっ！
What the...
Move aside!
えぐ…えぐ…。
Master, whatever is the matter?
（イザベラ）坊っちゃま！
どうされました！？
（焔王）どこに行ってたんじゃ。
余を置いて。
You left me alone... and
went off somewhere...
す　すいません　坊っちゃま！
ほら　ポテチー！
We're sorry, Master!
Here, have a potato chip!
お前たち　余…余のことは…。
You think I...
アウトオブ眼中なのかぁ～！！
You think I'm just cramping your style?!
（イザベラ）ぼ　坊っちゃま～！
M-Master?!
えぐ…えぐ…。
コホ　コホッ。
（早乙女）来やがったか。
They've come.
On the Brink! What'll We Do?!
ク～ッ　ウッ　キィ～。
あっ…。
次は　お前だ。
You're next.
テメエ…。
ブルッ　ダゥ…。
Why, you...
泣くんじゃねぇ　ベル坊。
ヒルダが見てんぞ。
ダー。
Don't cry, Baby Beel.
Hilda's watching.
坊っ…ちゃま。お逃げ下さい。
Master...
Please, escape.
イィ…。
《そのザマで
まだベル坊の心配かよ》
You're still worried about Baby
Beel after what happened to you?
上等だ。
Fine then.
（邦枝）ん…あっ！なっ　えっ？
ちょっと男鹿　何して…。
H-Hey, Oga, what are you-
（邦枝）ヒルダさん？
Hilda-san...
邦枝…ヒルダを頼む。
Kunieda. Take care of Hilda.
あ…。
あとで全部　説明するからよ。
I'll explain everything afterwards.
ヒルダのこと見ててくれ。
Watch over Hilda for me.
グゥ～ワァ～。
Spinning, spinning, spinning yogurty...
（神崎）♪～　グールグルグル
ヨーグルッチ～
♪～　神崎　一でグ～ルグ
Kanzaki Hajime is spinning...
ん？なんだ　ありゃ。
東条とメガネ会長？
What's this? Tojo and that 4-eyed Pres?
へえ～こんなとこでケンカか？
面白そうじゃねえか。
Oh? Fighting here?
This should be interesting.
I think I'll watch for a bit.
ちょっと見物すっか。
（由加）はぁ？
ん？
え？
（ズバン！）
Don't you think droppin' a heel on a
lady's head is kind of, like, rude?
女子の頭に　かかと落としは
ひどくないっスか？
Shut up!
うるせ～よ！何してんだ
こんなとこで。のぞきか？
What the hell are you doing here? Peeping?
（由加）神崎先輩こそ。
Same to you, Kanzaki-senpai!
I was just on my way home
from the supermarket nearby!
（神崎）オレは近くのスーパーに
行った帰りだよ。
Same for me!
ウチもっス！そしたら偶然
あの２人の声が聞こえてきて～。→
Then, I just happened to hear those two...
It looks like two guys're
fightin' over a woman!
１人の女を　２人の男が
取り合うみたいな→
な～んか　トライアングルラブな
感じが　パネぇんスけど。
It's so totally like a love-triangle, yeah!
で　どっちが勝ってんだ？
So, who'll win?
それが　おかしいんスよね。
ってゆ～か　パネぇんスよ。
あ？
That's what's strange.
I mean, it's crazy.
（由加）
ほら　なんか黒いじゃねぇっスか。
あのメガネ会長。→
Don't you think 4-eyed Pres
there's kinda... dark?
その黒さが　パナくなってから
強さが　パネぇんスよ！
The crazier that black stuff gets
the more crazy strong he gets!
ん…。
東条先輩もパネぇっスけど→
Tojo-senpai's pretty crazy too, so which
crazy's more crazy, Kanzaki-senpai?
神崎先輩は　どっちのパナさが
パネぇと思っ…。
I don't get what the hell you're sayin'!
何言ってっか　わかんね～んだよ！
パー子かテメエは！
You're the crazy bitch, crazy!
パー子ってなんスか？
パー子ってなんスか！？
Who're you callin' a crazy bitch?!
（東条）それも出馬八神流か？
Is that also part of the
Izuma 8 Spirits School?
（出馬）
フン。そろそろ　しまいにしよか。
楽しかったで。
Let's finish this.
It was fun. Let's do it again, Tojo Hidetora!
またやろうや　東条英虎。
（静）虎…。
Tora...
とどめやっ！
This is it!
（グラフェル）遅ぇ！
Too slow!
（静・東条）あっ…。
え？
あぁ…。
あっ…。
ダメだ。
話になんね～わ　こいつ。
Pointless. This guy's not worth the effort.
（ナーガ）魔力を感じて　もしやと思い
来てみたが　無駄足だったか。
We felt his power, so came just in case...
But it was a waste of time.
Yeah. He ain't up to Demon level.
（グラフェル）ああ　悪魔ってほど
悪魔じゃね～よ。
出来損ないだ。
Just a reject.
さしずめ　人間界に追放された
下級悪魔の子孫といったところか。
Perhaps a descendant of some lower Demon
that was banished to the Human World?
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division
Pillar Master: Naga
ちぇっ　やっぱ　ヘカドスの方へ
行っとくんだったな。
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Divison
Pillar Master: Graphel
I guess we should have
gone where Hecadoth went.
（アランドロン）お茶が入りましたよ～。
I've brought your beverage!
（ピシッ）
（アランドロン）あら！？不吉な…。
Oh?
That's not a good sign.
（古市）いや　何してんの　お前。
Um, what the hell are you doing?
ちゅめたい　お飲み物など
チュッ　いかがでちゅかな？
出ていけ！
How would you like a
refreshing, cool beverage?
Get out!
ガァー！！
あっ…。
フン。もう声も出んか？契約者。
Can't even talk anymore, Contract Holder?
ハァハァハァ…。
ン～ッシ。
（ヘカドス）貴様に恨みはないが→
I have nothing against you.
焔王様の敵となる以上
そろそろ消えてもらうぞ。
But as long as you remain Lord
En's enemy, I will eliminate you.
《やりづれぇ…あの得物。→
That weapon he's got is making this rough!
It's harder to close the distance
than I figured it would be.
想像以上に　こっちの間合いを
潰してきやがる》
男鹿！
来んなっ！
Oga!
Stay back!
あっ…。
This is my fight. Stay
quiet and watch over Hilda!
こいつは　オレのケンカだ！
黙ってヒルダ見てろ！
That's right, woman.
その通りだ　女。
むざむざ殺されに来るな。
Watch, helplessly, as he dies...
Behemoth's orders! This man must die!
ベヘモット様の命令は
この男の命のみだ！
くっ…！
遅い！！
Too late!
捉えた。
男鹿っ！
Got you.
Oga!
捉えたのは…。
Actually...
こっちの方だ！
ダー！
...I'm the one who got you!
ゼロ距離ならどうだ　こらぁ～！！
Let's see how you handle
one at point blank range!
ダ～ブ～！！
なんだ　あいつら。
いいとこなのに邪魔しやがって。
What's with those guys?
They barged in just when
things were getting good.
ちょ　今はなんかマズイですって！
Hey!
I don't think this is a good time!
あぁ？関係ね～よ。
はぁ？
Huh? What's it matter?
ぐおっ！？
もう少し　もう少し待ちましょう。
A little longer!
Let's wait a little longer!
ば…入ってる。
Tap out!
What the hell are they?
なんなの？こいつら…。
こいつらが本物の…。
These guys are real...
（出馬）((悪魔ですか？))
Demons?
（校長）((うむ　君とは違う
魔界生まれの本物じゃ))
Yes. Unlike you, they're real
ones born in the Demon World.
((それが…この街に来ると？))
And they're coming to this town?
((おそらくな。いいか　出馬君。
忠告しておくぞ。→
I suspect as much.
Listen well, Izuma-kun. I need to warn you.
奴らに会っても
絶対に手を出してはならん))
Do not fight them even if they confront you.
《すんません　校長。
アンタには感謝してます》
I'm sorry, Principal.
I owe you a lot.
（出馬）《前の学校で
悪魔の力を使てもて→
You're the one who took me
in when I had no where to go
行き場を失った僕を
拾ってくれたんは　アンタや。→
after using my Demon
powers at my last school.
同じような境遇の子がいることも
聖石矢魔に来て初めて知った。→
When I came to St. Ishiyama, it was the first
time I knew there were others in my situation.
でも　だからこそ
その忠告はきかれへん。→
But that's exactly why I
can't follow your advice.
だって　こいつら
男鹿君　消しに来たんやろ？》
Because these guys have
come to eliminate Oga-kun.
待ちぃ。
あ？
Hold it!
人の勝負に割り込んできて
挨拶なしかい。
You're going to break up our fight
and not even introduce yourselves?
《そうは…させへん》
I can't allow that.
やめとけ。
お前じゃ　相手になんね～よ。
Let it go. You're no match for us.
（出馬）どうやろか。
I wonder about that.
相手にならね～って。
I thought I said...
ぐわっ…。
（グラフェル）言ってんだろ！
...you're no match!
Peons like you should
know their place! Yeah?!
（グラフェル）
下っぱが調子ぶっこいてんじゃ
ねぇ～ぞ！？ああ！？
ガラ悪いな…。
Rude, aren't you?
（出馬）《なんちゅ～力や…
これが本物の悪魔かい》
What power... Is this what
a real Demon is like?
てめ～から
やってやろうか！？…ああ！？
You want me to start with you, huh?
放せ人間…
てめ～も　やられて～のか？
Unhand me, Human.
You wanna get beat, too?
東条…アカン！
Tojo... Don't!
（東条）人の獲物を…
取ってんじゃねぇよ！
Don't go takin' my mark!
Go, go, Gohan-kun...
（アランドロン）
♪～　ゆけゆけゴーゴー　ごはん…
（アランドロン）むっ！？んんっ…→
Perhaps a harbinger of bad things to come?
何か良くないことの
前触れでしょうか…。
What are you doing?
何してんだ？
I was just thinking of
changing into my pajamas...
（アランドロン）
あっ　いえ…寝巻きに
着替えようとしたのですが→
I've already finished making the bed!
あっ　ベッドメイキングは
済んでおります。
Now is not the time, or the
place... Or anything else!
場違いなんだよ
いろんな意味で！！
なっ…。
うぎゃ…。
さすがに今のは肝を冷やしたぞ。
You really did have me scared there.
か…片手で受け止めたのか？
He stopped it with one hand?
That was close, Contract Holder.
惜しかったな　契約者…消えろ。
Begone!
うわっ…。
はっ！？
Okay, that's enough.
（早乙女）は～い　そこまで。
うっ…。
Man, you're goin' nuts around town...
（早乙女）ったく…街中で
どかどか暴れやがって…。
Who the hell are you?
なんだ？貴様は…。
（早乙女）あ？→
Can't you tell, you piece of crap?
見りゃわかんだろ　くそったれ
そいつの先生だ。
I'm his teacher.
はっ！？
（神崎）おお…。
I said let go!
…ってえだろうが！
うお～…。
（東条）
Tora!
虎っ！
フン　ちょっと強ぇくらいの人間が悪魔に勝てると思ったか？
You think some better-than-average
human could win against a Demon?
Let's go, Graphel.
行くぞ　グラフェル。
I know.
わぁってるよ。
（東条）逃げん…じゃねぇよ。
You runnin' away?
あ…？
This ain't over yet.
（東条）まだ　終わりじゃねぇ…。
（東条）うっ…うう。
You really should have just stayed down.
素直に寝とけば
よかったのによぉ…。
Don't...
（静）それ以上…近づかないで！
...get any closer!
うっ…。
Oh, no!
アカン！
あっ…。
うう…くっ…。
Woman. You get in our way, and
we'll eliminate you first.
（グラフェル）女…邪魔すんなら
てめ～から消すぞ？
うう…くっ。
ああ～っ！
やばいっスよ　神崎先輩！→
This is bad, Kanzaki-senpai!
って…なに　気絶してんスか！？
（神崎）うう…。
Why are you passed out?!
Tora!
はっ？
（静）虎…。
Don't you lay a hand on her!
（東条）
こいつに触ってんじゃねぇよ！
（静）あっ…。
Move it.
どいてろ！
無茶だってば！
I told you not to overdo it!
Quiet.
うるせえ！
（グラフェル）ムカつくぜ　てめぇ…→
You're pissin' me off.
I hate guys who always talk
about "guts" and crap...
二言目には　根性とか言いそうな
オレの大嫌いなタイプだ。
（東条）ぐっ…。
フッ…。
A fluke?
（グラフェル）《まぐれか…？もう意識も飛んでんじゃね～か…》
Isn't he already unconscious?
うお～～！！
He's fighting on pure instinct?
（グラフェル）
《こいつ…闘争本能のみで…》
Tora!
虎っ！
もうええ…→
That's enough!
You're really gonna die like this!
これ以上やったら
ホンマに死んでまうで！
Hold it right there!
（神崎）待ちな！
You didn't have to kick me twice...
（由加）何も２回も蹴らなくても。
You did well, Tojo.
（神崎）よくやった　東条…
あとは　オレに任せとけ。
Leave the rest to me.
あっ…。
Who the hell are you?
なんだ　てめ～は？
フッ…
その言葉　そのまま返すぜ。
And I'll say the exact same thing to you.
Huh?
（グラフェル）あ？
てめえ　どこの
学校のもんだこらぁ！
Which school are you from, punk?!
I ain't never seen a
uniform like that before!
見慣れね～　制服着やがってあれか！修学旅行か！
You guys on a field trip or somethin'?
アホ。
Idiot...
You're about to tangle with the
boss of Ishiyama, Kanzaki Hajime!
こっからは石矢魔のボス
神崎　一が相手になってやんよ！
（由加）
うお～　神崎先輩　パネぇっス。→
Kanzaki-senpai, that's crazy!
Stealin' the spotlight, all hyena-like!
おいしいとこだけ！
マジ　ハイエナっス！
フッ　おうよ。次
ハイエナっつったらブッ飛ばす。
Yeah!
And the next time you say
hyena I'll kick your ass.
Now we got a bunch of idiots
who think they're hot stuff.
（グラフェル）
バカどもが調子に乗りやがって…
まとめて血祭りにしてやるよ。
I'll turn you all into mincemeat!
（ビシッ！）
んっ？→
何だよ　気味悪り～な。
んっ！？…うわっ。
What? That's not a good sign.
（ほのか）あっ…。
Honoka?
あっ　ほのか…どうした？
って　いや…違うぞ！→
What is it?
Um, it's not...
The big guy was wearing this for me!
これは　おっさんが
オレのために着るって…違う！
I mean it's not like...
あっ…。
Hey!
お～いいい…！？
You're...
お前は…。
Saotome...-sensei?
早乙女先生…。
I don't know who you are, but if you
get in my way, I won't hold back.
何者かは知らんが
邪魔立てするなら容赦せんぞ。
フン…常套句　並べやがって→
That's pretty clichéd of you.
もうちょっと考えて
喋った方がいいぞ…お前。
Try thinking a little more before you speak.
What?
何…？
And it looks like you've done a
real number on my students here.
（早乙女）それにしても
こりゃまた　ずいぶんと→
オレの生徒を
いじめてくれたじゃね～か→
Right, you piece of crap?
ええ？くそったれ…
お仕置きしちゃうぞ。
I'm gonna punish you good.
What is this overwhelming pressure?
（ヘカドス）
《なんだ　この圧迫感は…？→
My gut tells me to proceed with caution.
直感が警告してくる
この男は危険だ→
This man is dangerous.
I have to get rid of him immediately, or...
今のうちに始末して
おかなければ…》
I'll ask you once more.
（ヘカドス）
もう一度だけ聞く　貴様…何者だ？
Who are you?
おいおい　人にものを尋ねる時は→
Whoa there...
Didn't your granny teach you to put down
your spear when you're talking to people?
まず　槍をしまうって
ばあちゃんに言われなかったか？
Unfortunately...
生憎だな…
オレが生まれる前に死んでたよ！
...she was dead before I was born!
Oh, pardon me!
そいつは…失礼！
（ヘカドス）ううっ…。
なっ…。
Fine, then I'll teach you.
じゃあ　オレが教えてやるよ。
な…んだ
このケタはずれの魔力は…！
What's this incredible Demon power?!
…あん？
It's in Hecadoth's direction.
ヘカドスのいる方角だな…。
ありえねぇっ！→
I can't believe this!
Is there anyone in the Human
World with such Demon power?
こんな魔力を持った奴が
人間界にいるのか！？
I think Hecadoth might be in over his head.
確かに…
ヘカドス１人では荷が重いな。→
Enough playing around.
遊びは終わりだ
あちらに合流する。
（グラフェル）ちっ！
We'll meet up there.
Hold it, you!
（神崎）
待てコラ　逃げんじゃね～よ！
Turnin' tail?
てめえとの決着はお預けだ→
We'll finish with you later.
Be glad you're still alive, Humans.
命拾いしたな…人間！
（神崎）フッ…口ほどにもねぇ。→
All talk.
They got scared of my aura and ran off.
オレのオーラに
びびって逃げやがった。
Seriously?
マ…マジっスか！？
パネぇっスよ！
That's crazy! Hayena-senpai, you're crazy!
ハイエナ先輩　パネぇっス！
だから　誰がハイエナだ　こらぁ！
Who the hell're you callin' a hyena?!
悪魔か…
聞きたいことは山ほどあるけど→
Demons, huh?
I've got a lot to ask you, but
treating your wounds comes first.
とりあえず　手当てが先ね。
すまんな。
Sorry...
And you take things way too far.
あんたは　無茶しすぎ。→
図体ばっか　でかくなって　中身は何も変わってないんだから。
You might've gotten big, but you
haven't changed one bit on the inside.
（東条）フン…おめえもな。
Same with you.
What's that?
《なんだ！？…ゼブルスペル？》
A Zebel Spell?
No way... A Spellmaster?
まさか…スペルマスター！？
A contract with a Demon not on equal terms...
（ヘカドス）
《悪魔と対等以上の契約を交わし
使役（しえき）する者…》
...where he's in control!
They still exist?
まだ　存在していたのか？→
I thought they had all long perished
as relics from the old days!
とっくに
消え去った前時代の遺物だぞ！？
I'm still here!
（早乙女）消えてね～よ。
恐竜みたいに言うな。
Don't make me sound like a dinosaur.
And wait... That mark...
しかも　貴様…その紋章は！！
ん！？
ったく　次から次へと…
ご近所さんに迷惑だぞ　お前ら。
Right from one to the next...
You people are disturbing the neighborhood!
You stirred up the hornet's nest, Hecadoth.
やぶへびじゃね～か　ヘカドス
とんだ大蛇が出てきたもんだ。
And out came the queen.
フン…。
A Spellmaster, huh?
スペルマスターか…
３人がかりで行くぞ。
The three of us will take you on.
おいおいおい…。
Whoa...
Watch closely, Oga.
よ～く見とけよ　男鹿。
特別授業だ…→
This is a special lesson.
こいつの使い方を見せてやるよ。
I'll show you the right way to use this.
Here we go!
行くぞ！
For Demons #1:
悪魔のための　その１→
Keep your arms tucked in,
feet at shoulder width...
脇を締めて　足は肩幅だ。
（３人）うっ…。
Go tell Behemoth...
ベヘモットに言っとけ→
Wait a little longer!
もう　ちっとばかし
待ってろってなっ！
んっ…。
はっ。
（邦枝）
They went back?
帰ったか…。
あっ…ああ…。
アウッ…。
あっ…。
ああ…。
ダブッ…。
Now then, the real problem begins.
さてっと　問題はこれからだな。ん？にょ。
Hey, Oga...
おい　男鹿
とぼけてないで手伝え。→
Don't just stand there! Help out.
If we don't do something about Miss
Boobs here, she'll be in real danger.
あのボインの　ねえちゃん
何とかしねぇと相当やべぇぞ。
大丈夫よ
私たちが絶対　助けるから。
Don't worry.
We will definitely save her.
Huh?
なんだ？
Alaindelon?
アラン…ドロン？
Honestly...
（アランドロン・ラミア）
ったく…ヒルダ姉さま
１人守れないなんて…。
You can't even protect Miss Hilda?
（ラミア）このボンクラ。
You blockhead.
A black cat crossed my path!
My shoelaces snapped!
And even the stalks in my tea split in two!
So many bad omens!
What's your problem?
Anyway, what'll we do, Oga?
Those guys are sure to come back again.
Isn't it obvious?
There's only one thing to do
when you want to get stronger!
If a black cat's about to cross
your path, quickly turn around!
On the next Beelzebub:
It's Time for Training!
Training at my shrine?
Could it be... Secret special
training, just you and me?